itbinternet.com 2008-06-17

# IT Backbones - Commerce, Featuring News, Press Releases, IT Directory & Links

## Privacy Policy

On registration, IT Backbones requests some personal information - including the candidate’s name, email address, telephone number and company name. IT Backbones may occasionally use this information for a number of specific purposes: to contact registered users regarding our advertising services, improve our services, conduct research or provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

IT Backbones does not rent, sell, or share personal information regarding registered users of the network with other companies or individuals. IT Backbones does not provide any personal information to advertising partners when the user interacts with, or views, an advert.

## Confidentiality and Security

Access to IT Backbones registered users’ personal information is highly restricted; only employees that are required to utilise this information are granted access. The IT Backbones database containing registered user information is not held on any physical site but within a secure online server. State of the art safeguards for this server include secure I.P. access and encryption.

If you have any questions regarding privacy or security on IT Backbones, please email: [security@itbackbones.com](mailto:security@itbackbones.com)

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

IT Backbones reserves the right to update this policy as required. If this policy is updated, registered users will be notified by email and the updates will be listed on the website.

##### More Video News
